I really didn't think I was going to have
a good time, but I did. Totally did.
I love camping.
Anything can happen.
It wasn't camping, it was more of
a wilderness retreat.
- Morning.
- Michael.
Ryan invited some of the branch managers
and Toby into the woods
for a "get to know you" weekend.
Michael wasn't invited.
Apparently they already knew everything
they needed to know about him.
Did you sleep in cabins?
Under the stars. It was really
beautiful, you should come.
Bob and I
took rock climbing lessons once.
Michael wasn't invited
on Ryan's camping trip.
Toby went,
but Michael didn't go.
He wasn't invited.
- Who went?
- Me, Dan from Buffalo,
Mark Gism, Jeff from Albany
and Ryan, obviously.
Made so many s'mores,
that I finally had to say,
"No more s'mores,
no more s'mores."
Ryan invited me to go
on his wilderness adventure retreat.
It was this amazing
beautiful experience...
- Hey, nobody cares.
Nobody cares. I need that room
at some point, so just,
wrap it up.
Michael wasn't invited.
Subtitles by Aimee
www.TusSeries.com
Resync:
nadielostzilla.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
4x07 'Survivor man'
Hypothetically,
if I were to ask you to go camping,
and you know what hypothetical means?
- Not real.
- Got it.
So if I were to hypothetically
ask you to go camping
with me, would you go?
- Absolutely, yes.
When Michael plays
the hypothetical game, I always say yes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You wanna go today?
And I am always busy.
Oh, can't go today,
'cause I'm donating blood.
How often
can you actually donate blood?
- Is there a limit? I don't...
- Your body only has a certain amount.
Well, is that it, or...?
Yeah, just this whole Toby camping thing,
I don't know, seems a little lame.
How so?
A bunch of guys, in a tent?
Making s'mores?
- What's that?
- Hello, I'm Broken Mountain.
Here's the thing.
That's not how you go camping.
- I think you go camping by yourself...
- Right.
In the wilderness. It's not with a group
of guys frolicking around in tents.
It's one guy, or two guys,
if your plans change.
- Not gonna change.
- I wanna do it myself.
You know, I want to go and, and
find out something about myself,
I wanna get outta here.
All the cliques,
and the office politics.
Fluorescent lights. Asbestos.
- I thought we had that looked at. - I'm
sick of it Jim. I'm sick of this place.
When Jan and I had satellite,
we used to watch a reality show
called "Survivorman."
And...
it was interesting
because it was about a guy
who would go out
in the middle of no where
and just try not to die,
try not to get eaten
by an animal, or...
be overexposed.
OK, I will only need two things:
roll of duct tape and a knife.
- I'm on it.
- OK.
Thirty minutes or less,
please come back.
Save the receipts.
Hey, what are...?
Let's see if any of these will work.
I keep various weaponries
strategically placed around the office.
I saved Jim's life with a can
of pepper spray
I had velcroed under my desk.
People say,
"Oh, it's dangerous to keep weapons
in the home or the work place."
Well I say, "It's better to be hurt
by someone you know accidentally,
than by a stranger
on purpose."
Dwight and I are going out.
He will return later,
but I will not.
I will also be taking
a personal day tomorrow,
and perhaps the next day.
Do you want me to ask
where you're going?
- No.
- Great.
Dwight will be driving me
deep into the Pennsylvania wilderness.
Where he will then leave me
to either die or to survive.
The choice is yours.
No, the choice is actually yours.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yes, and I am leaving you
in charge of the office
for the rest of the day and
for the next several days.
Do not try to follow me.
- OK, great.
This is a very personal
private experience in the wild,
that I wish to share
with me, myself and I.
When I return, I hope to be
a completely changed human being.
That'd be great.
Do I believe that Michael
possesses the skills...
to survive
in a hostile environment?
Let's put it this way:
no, I do not.
This is what
a true survivor man does.
You simulate a disaster,
like a plane wreck.
You could only wear the clothes
that you have on,
and you could only use the stuff
you have in your pockets.
Now, in this case,
this disaster is a serial killer.
Creepy guy who's abducted me
and is taking me out into the
wilderness to leave me for dead.
No, I would never
leave you for dead.
- You would never escape.
-Well, yes I would. And I would survive.
I would make sure
that you were dead.
Then I would remove your teeth
and cut off your fingertips
so you could not be identified.
And they would call me
the Overkill Killer.
You are as creepy
as a real serial killer.
For real. Ok.
- What are you doing?
- I am putting this on
so I have no familiarity
with my surroundings.
Now this way,
I can't retrace my steps.
I don't know
what streets we've been...
What are you doing?
It would be better
if you were unconscious.
No! Gosh! Dwight.
Stop it, stop it! Stop it!
Do you want to
do this right or not?
Please allow me to have
one cathartic experience in my life.
Jim, we need to order a cake
for Creed's birthday.
Wasn't it just someone's birthday?
Yes. Kelly's was last week,
remember?
I do remember, yeah.
It's birthday month.
Creed's is today.
Oscar's is week after next.
Meredith's is at the end of the month.
Michael usually goes
with red and white streamers...
I have an idea. Why don't we just
do one big shared party?
What?
There are thirteen people
working in this office,
so thirteen times a year
Michael gets a cake
and balloons,
and some sort of joke gift
and makes a toast.
One is a joke
about how old you are.
Look at those wrinkles.
Blacks do crack!
Not crack the drug.
And the other
is something inappropriate.
Or horrible. Or both.
What else? He only sings
the high harmony to "Happy Birthday."
And he's a very big believer
in surprise parties.
Maybe even, arguably,
possibly to a fault.
Happy Birthday!
So I think, yeah,
I think getting these out of the way
might be productive.
We can just have
one big fun party.
Where everybody's happy
and nobody wastes their time.
I don't like it.
You're shaking things up
a bit, huh?
It's a pretty good idea,
don't you think?
- Do you think it's a good idea?
- No...
I think it's a great idea.
We're here.
Dwight will take my blindfold off
when we are deep in the forest.
Just the two of us
from this point out.
Here we go. Just the two of us.
Here we go, into the wild.
To the mighty forest.
Can you smell the trees
and the nature?
Keep going, you're fine.
Just some bushes
and some thickets.
Keep going.
You wanted wilderness,
you got it.
You know, try sending them
another invoice.
Did you see my memo
by the way?
"Let's be honest, as fun as birthdays
are, we could all use a break
from the constant cake, so let's
celebrate birthday month in style today."
This is really cool.
- Right? I was just thinking...
- No, totally, totally.
This way we get it all out of the way
at once and it could actually be fun.
Right! Exactly.
Knew I could count on you.
Good a spot as any.
What are you doing?
Stop it. Dwight, Dwight. Just...
- I'm just...
- Stop.
- Spin.
I'm trying to confuse
your sense of direction.
Behold.
- Alright, good. Thank you, Dwight.
- Here's your knife.
- Thank you.
- And here's your duct tape.
Alright, very good.
- Good luck, Michael.
- Thanks for the ride.
Leave me be, Dwight.
- Jim, can I have my own cake?
- What's that?
I really prefer
devils food cake.
- Oh, sure.
- Yes!
Wow! That was easy.
Yeah, people like me, I guess.
- I hate devils food.
- Well I think Meredith was just...
Screw Meredith.
I don't think it's fair
to let someone else pick the cake
on my birthday.
- Everybody's birthday.
- Today is actually my birthday
and I want to pick the cake.
- What do you want?
- I want pie. I want peach pie.
- You want a birthday pie?
I want a nice cobbler.
I'm gonna to talk to Angela and we're
gonna see what we can do about a pie.
I don't care who you talk to.
Just make it happen.
- It will be Angela.
- You tell her it's for Creed.
She'll know
what that means.
Day One.
I'm in the interior of
the vast Pennsylvania wilderness.
I've brought with me
only the bare essentials.
A knife, roll of duct tape,
in case I need to craft some shelter
or make some sort of water vessel.
It's hot today.
The sun is in the two-thirds
easterly quadrant,
which would make it about
2 o'clock in the afternoon.
It's really beating down
on me now.
I think that I want to get
a little more comfortable
because the sun
is depleting my resources.
There we go.
Watch that I don't hit
my corroded artery here...
I lied to Michael.
I said that I would leave him alone,
but I will not.
I will remain close by to provide
unseen moral support,
but I will never help him.
I will let harm befall him.
I will even let him die.
But I will never
let him lose his dignity.
There we go.
Much better.
Now everything I brought with me
can be used.
My sport coat here
can be fashioned
into a backpack of sorts.
I'm going to wear
what was once one of my pant legs.
See, this is
a beautiful piece of material.
This could be used
for all sorts of things.
Some sort of kerchief
to keep my neck
nice and comfortable.
- Tuna.
- Andy.
Me likey the ice cream cake, okay?
- Fudgey the Whale.
- Not your birthday.
Well, I'm just saying, you know,
if you want to make people happy,
namely me,
you will have a Fudgey the Whale.
Alright, I'll look into it,
but the answer's no.
Wow, OK, harsh.
Just don't expect me to show up.
Andy, I have some calls to make.
- Loud and clear.
- Alright.
Pizza rolls.
OK, I'm gonna go into this office here
to do some work.
- So I will be in here.
- Mushroom caps.
I am totally alone right now,
with only my thoughts.
I love it. I'm loving it.
I can literally say anything I want.
No one is gonna here me.
Wish I could have gone with Ryan
on that cool retreat!
Jan has plastic boobs!
I HAVE HEMORRHOIDS!
Doesn't even matter.
Michael is a man
of great depth and passion.
I don't know
what he's searching for out here.
I hope he finds it.
Lunch.
Well, it is a little chillier
than I had thought,
so I have fashioned my hat
back into my pants.
Several hours in, time for me
to find some nourishment.
Now, these woods are full of creatures
that can sustain human life.
Things like, uh, squirrels,
nice juicy rabbit
would be delicious.
About two more minutes.
I have made this spear,
with which I will impale my dinner.
And it couldn't come
a moment too soon
because I have been
without food for a good
three hours or so.
I'm startin' to feel it a little bit.
It's Creed's birthday today.
Happy Birthday to you.
Happy Birthday, dear Creed.
Happy birthday, buddy.
What is Jim thinking?
It's a birthday,
so what if there's a lot of them?
Yeah, I work hard all day.
I like knowing that
there's going to be a break.
Most days I just sit
and wait for the break.
I took an extra shot of insulin
in preparation for this cake today.
If I don't have
some cake soon, I might die.
- Why don't you just have an apple?
- Why don't you mind your business?
Listen, I figured this out.
Jimmy had his birthday three weeks ago,
so he doesn't care.
- Probably went to his head.
- Yeah.
Hey guys,
what're we talking about?
Nothing!
Nothing going on.
We're talking about nothing.
C'mon, gang.
Well if you take a look at this,
I tented my pants.
I've made myself
a nice pants tent shelter.
And this little guy may be
Dunder Mifflin paper some day.
Nothing to worry about.
Just using the scope.
Safety is...
on.
Hey, I just got the word
on the communal birthdays.
Great idea.
- Oh, thanks man.
- Yeah...
- Is there anything...?
- My birthday was two months ago.
- There was no party.
- What?
Well, it... there was.
But Michael scheduled it for...
4:58 on a Friday. You know,
people sang in the parking lot.
- I remember that.
- I don't know, I just thought...
you could include me.
- Seriously?
I just though you could add me.
I don't see the harm in that.
Toby's great. He's great,
but sometimes
he can be a little bit much.
"I don't see the harm in that."
Well, it's a cake Toby, so, c'mon.
OK. Yeah, you know what?,
we're just gonna throw you in.
Because more the merrier, right?
No. No way.
I am not a machine, Jim.
You can't just
change plans willy nilly
and expect these little magic party
elves to do your bidding.
We already have devils food,
peach cobbler,
Fudgey the Whale,
mushroom caps.
I'm allergic to mushrooms.
That's a bummer.
OK, then we need to...
Hey everybody.
Hi, how you doing?
Can I have
your attention please?
'Cause we have to talk
about this birthday thing.
- Conference room?
- Yes, conference room in 5 minutes.
We're gonna solve it
right here.
We're actually
gonna talk about it out here.
So, who has problems
with the birthday thing?
One, two, three, everybody.
OK, so then
we just shouldn't do it.
What am I supposed to do
with two cakes and a pie?
I'll take 'em.
Well nobody's
touching my cobbler.
Hey, Michael. I mean Jim.
Yup, Phyllis called me Michael.
And I will always and forever
be haunted by that fact.
Under this tree,
I think I struck the mother load.
Those are nature's
best mushrooms.
Wild, and I have to say
these little buggers
are damn tasty as well.
Get them out.
Happy Birthday to you.
Happy Birthday, dear Creed.
Yeah!
Alright, skip around the room.
Skip around the room.
We want...
Alright. Yeah, don't do that.
You're gonna break something.
Man became civilized for a reason.
He decided that he liked
to have warmth, and clothing,
and television
and hamburgers,
and to walk upright,
and to have a soft futon
at the end of the day.
He didn't want to have
to struggle to survive.
I don't need the woods.
I have a nice wood desk.
I don't need fresh air, because
I have the freshest air around,
A.C.
And I don't need
wide open spaces.
Check it out.
I can also make it the sky.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey.
What up?
Sure glad you're back.
- You are relieved.
- You have no idea.
So what did I miss?
Well, I tried to put all
the birthdays together at once.
Terrible idea.
Yeah, okay, I did that.
Rookie mistake.
You did do it?
Just wait. Ten years,
you'll figure it out.
I don't think I'll be here
in ten years.
That's what I said.
That's what she said.
That's what who said?
I never know.
I just say it.
I say stuff like that, you know,
to lighten the tension.
- When things sort of get hard.
- That's what she said.
Nice.
Really good.
Bravo, my young ward.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org