Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- previously on dexter...
- it's for sure.
i'm pregnant.
- what kind of father
would i be?
After all, i kill people.
- aah!
- me?
demented daddy dexter.
- [moaning]
- this child is happening.
But your role in its life
is entirely up to you.
- yesterday morning you said
when the case ends, we end.
- i thought you understood
when we got involved.
I track killers.
that's what i do.
A pattern of bodies
was identified in oregon.
My flight leaves tonight.
- if you're leaving,
we gotta work out logistics.
- do you honestly want
to go down this path?
- i don't know if i'm going
to be a father to the kid.
- how could even say you're not
gonna be a father to that kid?
I mean, where would you be
without harry?
- harry knew my mother.
Laura moser was his informant.
Was he just using her?
Was he using me?
Dad wasn't perfect, deb.
- what did he do?
cheat on mom?
Bullshit.
who?
I need all the records you have
On my dad's
confidential informants.
- attractive female c.i.s?
- why, you know something?
- there's a good reason
why quinn's of interest to i.a.
- internal affairs
is investigating you.
Is there something
you're not telling us?
- anton is not officially
a c.i.
- what do you mean?
- i never filed
an arrest report on him.
- you are the best thing
that has happened to me.
- just sending out my positive
intentions to our baby.
You know, we're connected.
You're what makes me real.
Please say yes.
- yes, we will marry you.
Syl has offered
to list my house
So we can buy something bigger.
- better hope she doesn't insist
on a place with central air.
- i was actually thinking
i might keep my place.
- "no" doesn't really work
in a relationship, dexter.
- every man needs his privacy.
Some more than others.
- is it possible
i've actually made a friend?
Someone i can trust
with my dark secrets?
- i didn't teach you the code
to share with your buddies.
- miguel really did it.
and i taught him how.
Harry was right.
he used me.
You're all just
unchecked versions of myself,
What i would've become
without my father's code.
- [strangled scream]
- i could kill you now.
- i've never felt this.
- you've never
had a son before.
You want to see him
come into the world.
- yes. i've never wanted
anything so much in my life.
[sirens]
I have moved on
from my father.
But i still need his code.
But right now,
life is good.
Dexter morgan, family man.
Tonight's the night.
The night when a primal,
sacred need
Calls to me.
I've waited and waited.
But tonight,
this night...
It's time.
Tonight's the night
i finally...
Sleep.
[creak]
- [gasps, screams]
No...
[screaming]
- [baby cries]
- [sighs]
- [crying]
- oh, okay, harrison.
The driving thing didn't work.
The singing thing
didn't work.
You planning on both of us
not sleeping
For another three months?
- [crying]
- apparently so.
Okay,
i want to take you inside,
But i don't want you
waking mommy.
Hey.
If you could talk,
you'd tell me not to worry
About you, right?
- no...
[sobbing]
oh, please...
No, don't...
No...
Please...
Please...please...
- shh.
It's already over.
- [gasps]
[groaning and whimpering]
[quirky music]
[record scratch]
[off-kilter dexter theme]
? ?
- [yawns]
- marco!
- polo.
- marco.
- there's this cliche
where serial killers
Are always described as,
"quiet, kept to himself.
Kind of a loner."
[toy squeaks]
It's a cliche for a reason.
[pop music playing]
Has anybody seen my keys?
- astor, i asked you
to keep it down.
- [sighs]
- why do you hate my music
so much?
- i don't hate your music.
- you don't?
- cody, get out
of the larsons' pool.
It's time for school.
- if i had an ipod,
You wouldn't have to listen
to my stuff.
- you want an ipod,
earn one.
Do your chores.
unpack your room.
- god, you are so unfair!
- did you get any sleep?
- an hour and a half,
maybe.
- oh, and you have court.
Look, i appreciate you
taking the night shift,
But when you have a big day
like today,
It's okay to wake me up.
- well, it's kind of
On-the-job training,
you know?
- all that matters
is his father's there for him.
- i cannot find keys...
- cody!
Astor, the music.
You usually leave them
right here by the phone.
- i know.
- school. clothes. now.
- sorry.
- you don't get some sleep,
it won't be your keys
That get lost--
it'll be your mind.
- i lost that years ago.
Dexter morgan,
good suburban husband.
Happy father of three.
On paper, anyway.
[kids laughing]
- hey, dex, what's the news?
- uh, too soon to tell.
- dexter?
Dexter, you forgot
your cell phone.
Oh, good morning, elliot.
- another beautiful day.
More pool time
for the kids.
- well, you already took
the morning shift,
So i'll watch them
this afternoon.
- takes a village.
- [chuckles]
- [roars]
- [shrieks]
- ah.
Mm.
- take that!
- carpools and swimming pools.
How much
are we living the dream?
- so much.
- [laughs]
- living the dream.
- oh...
- [smooching]
Mm.
Hey, um, do you think you can
tivo jon stewart for me?
Mm.
- thinking about
jon stewart, huh?
- [chuckles]
Well, he is handsome.
- [giggles]
- and funny.
- i love you.
Oh, fuck me.
- that's kind of where this
is heading.
- no.
i'm late for work.
- [sighs]
It's a good thing you moved in,
or i'd never see you.
- well, one of us
has to live here.
- at least
with the cruise ship,
I get to see you
every few days.
I went on tour...
- i know.
It's okay,
i kind of like it.
Keeps you from getting sick
of me.
- that's never going
to happen.
- yeah, because
you're never here.
- no, because
you make me happy.
- and what conclusions
did you draw
From the blood evidence,
mr. morgan?
- i was able to determine
The victim's movement
and direction
After the initial
blunt force trauma to the head
Caused by the defendant's fist.
- how so?
- i...reconstructed, uh...
Timeline
and sequence of events
By examining...
it's here somewhere.
I noticed a passive
flow pattern bloodstain
Approximately
two meters in length
Emanating from
the head wound,
And the sample was consistent
With the sample
from the defendant's shirt.
- you did say "passive
flow pattern bloodstain"?
- quote, unquote.
- what exactly
do your notes say?
- um...
"the bloodstain described
a passive pooling
"and flow configuration,
type 'o' negative,
"matching the sample taken
from, um...
Uh...leonetti's shirt."
But this is the gomez hearing.
- yes, mr. morgan.
The defendant's name
is benito gomez.
- [sighs]
I must've brought
the wrong notes.
- do you frequently become
confused and disoriented
When conducting your spatter
analysis, mr. morgan?
- no, i do not.
We...just had a new baby.
Things were a little hectic
this morning.
- so you're saying
that you're sleep-deprived
And it's affecting
your judgment?
- no, it's just
a momentary mix-up.
- wrong notes,
wrong blood type.
Wrong defendant.
wrong case.
That's what you call
A momentary mix-up
in a murder trial?
- i misspoke.
- oh, fuck.
- your honor, the witness
Has just demonstrated
how unreliable he is
In a courtroom.
I would have to ask
How reliable his work is
in the lab.
Or on a crime scene.
Moreover, how reliable
is a police department
That would place so much trust
in his "expert" opinion?
- i'm halfway through
the c.i. files you gave me.
- i were you,
i'd spend more time
With that man of yours
and less time
Looking for some
old confidential informant
Your daddy might've diddled
back in the day.
- i meet another one tomorrow.
Maybe then i'll finally get
some answers.
- say you do.
Then what?
- then...i'll know.
That my perfect fucking father
wasn't so fucking perfect.
- so that's what,
the meaning of life?
- the meaning of my life.
- hey, buddy.
Guess where i was yesterday.
- well, i'm not sure, i...
- i was at a store.
Want to take a guess
what kind of store?
- i don't know.
grocery?
- clothing. you know me,
i'm pretty into that shit.
Gotta come correct and all.
but not yesterday.
- look, if this is about--
- come on, buddy.
let me finish.
I was at a store
helping a lady pick out
A suit for her son.
Know why?
because he had to be in court.
See the guy
who killed his old man.
Kid's first fucking suit.
Something a father
should be doing.
- i'm sorry.
- little late for "sorry."
That asshole you let walk?
- benito gomez.
- ah, now you get it right.
You actually see
what that fuckhead did?
Gomez hit the kid's old man
so hard,
His cheekbone broke,
pushing his eyeball up
And out of his face.
Then gomez,
sweetheart that he is,
Kills the guy
in front of his own son.
- i know.
- how about this beauty?
Gomez did five years
for beating his girlfriend
So bad even her dentist
had a hard time with the i.d.
So is your "sorry"
gonna keep gomez
From pounding somebody else
into the next world?
- jesus, chill out, quinn.
- no, deb, he's right.
i screwed up in court today.
Gomez walked.
this one's on me.
- thanks.
that means so much to me.
Why don't you hold onto those
for me, 'kay, buddy?
I'm sick of looking at 'em.
- you screwed up?
- big time.
- should i be worried?
- [sighs]
No, i'll be okay.
Maybe it's benny gomez
who should be worried.
- and good solve
on the reynolds case, guys.
Next up,
chief's office wants...
- anything i can do to keep
that angry irish off your ass,
Let me know.
- you're a real friend, vince.
[deep breath]
Quinn's a good cop.
I need a good kill.
And sometimes one just falls
into your lap.
- we've got a body
in kendall.
Morgan, quinn, you're up.
And dexter.
there's blood.
Lots of blood.
- talk about your bloodbath.
[chuckles]
Tough room.
Okay, femoral artery severed.
she bled out in minutes.
- suicide?
- no weapon on the premises.
- exactly. the coroner can suck
my uncircumcised dick
If he doesn't rule this
a homicide.
- that's way t.m.i.,
masuka.
Employment records show she just
got promoted to sous chef.
- a total babe.
and she could cook.
Had it all going on.
- then this.
- it's a very well-organized
crime scene.
The assailant took his time.
Cleaned up after himself.
Obviously doesn't have kids.
- keep an eye
on our expert witness.
In case our girl's parents
actually want to see
Someone go to jail for doing
this to their daughter.
- harsh.
[chatter over police radio]
- christine hill,
broward journal dispatch.
- and?
- and was ms. bell
the only victim?
- who gave you her name?
- i searched the address
On this thing
called the internet.
Now, what can you tell me
about the murder?
Suspects?
- murder? suspects?
We still haven't officially
ruled out suicide.
- so it was pills?
- no.
- then she bled out.
Women pretty much
only do one or the other.
- do me a favor.
You break this case
before we do, give me a call.
- it's detective joseph quinn.
Miami-metro,
extension 3734.
Cell number?
- mm.
- nice touch, joseph.
- damn it.
Can't anyone fill up the...
Fucking...
water thing?
- [chuckles]
Tough crime scene?
- no.
Mm...kind of.
Yes.
You know,
when things are going good,
I think that's god's way
of saying to cover your ass,
Because something's gonna
jump up and bite it, hard.
- well put.
You and anton doing okay?
- knock on wood.
- any sign your ass
is gonna get bit?
- none.
- so this is you
just making yourself crazy?
- that's kind of what i do.
What?
- it's just
i've taken that trip
1,000 times before.
- and?
- and knock it off.
- is that an order, boss?
- just some free advice
from someone
Who's been there before.
- hey, did you ever go out
with that guy that anton
Wanted you to meet?
- [scoffs]
Musicians
aren't really my thing.
- he owns a restaurant.
three of 'em.
Cuban restaurants.
What the fuck is wrong
with musicians?
- that came out wrong.
What makes you think
a cuban restaurant matters?
- that came out wrong too.
- i'm not looking
for anyone new anyway.
But when and if,
i'll let you know.
Thanks.
- mm-hmm.
- [yawns]
Finally.
peace and quiet.
No crying baby.
No marco, no polo.
Just me...and blood.
And mr. benito gomez.
Where to find a washed-up boxer
like you?
Trailer park.
great.
Kids, neighbors.
More kids.
Sounds like my world.
But this...
The only still open
for business establishment
In a lonely strip mall?
That's kind of calling to me.
This feels good.
[phone rings]
Hey, you.
- hey, dex.
you alone?
- uh, yeah. why?
- well, harrison won't go down
for his nap.
- surprise, surprise.
- you think maybe
you could sing to him?
- you bet.
- okay.
All right,
we're gonna put you on speaker.
- [crying]
- ? oh, beautiful
for spacious skies ?
? for amber waves ?
- shh.
- ? of grain ?
? for purple mountain
majesty ?
? above the fruited plain ?
? america, america,
god-- ?
- he's finally calming.
Thank you, dexter.
We love you.
- me too.
First up today,
finish the lisa bell blood work.
Tonight, a little
benny gomez recon.
Then go home and sing
the last 95 verses
of america the beautiful
to my baby son.
Who knew life could get so...
unsimple?
[deep breath]
I can deal.
i can deal.
- yo, quinn.
Boobs plus drinks equals...
- titty bar.
can't. got a date.
- [sighs]
Eh.
how about you, morgan?
Stud muffin still out of town?
- it's tempting, masuka.
And elegant.
Fuck off and die.
then die again.
- so that's a no.
I am feeling no love here,
folks.
- then it's working.
- hey, slacker.
half day?
- this is me leaving, vince.
i do it every day.
- but every day
wasn't like today.
What you went through?
come on.
Drinks are on me.
it'll cheer you up!
- i'm not uncheered.
- yeah?
tell that to your face.
- i'm going home
to my family.
- vastly overrated.
- just got a call
from robbery.
Some guy on his honeymoon
took a shot in the head.
Grave condition.
They're pulling the plug
tomorrow.
- nice fucking wedding gift.
- [sighs]
yeah.
The file is gonna land
on my desk
First thing in the morning.
And robbery's got squat.
It's gonna be
a total goatfuck.
- it sounds like
you need a drink, papi.
- you know what, vince?
I can use a cuervo.
or ten.
- [laughter]
[upbeat latin music]
? ?
- my dark passenger
is like a trapped coal miner.
Always tapping,
always letting me know
It's still in there,
still alive.
Quinn's legwork
may have shown me
Where to find our friend,
But this, benny--
My blood work is the stuff
that seals your fate.
[music and chatter inside bar]
No security cameras.
Parks away from the lights.
You just come and go
as you please.
But as of tomorrow night,
those days are over.
- i wasn't sure
you'd actually come by.
- put in my face time
with masuka.
And then i came to where
i really wanted to be.
- tell me again
this isn't crazy.
- yeah, it's crazy.
Crazy good.
[both laughing]
- keep shooting.
He's so sweet
when he's sleeping.
- we were all like that once.
Pure and innocent.
But then we grow up...
And things happen.
- well,
nothing's going to happen.
Not when he has a great dad
watching over him.
- yeah, he's a lucky guy.
[loud pop music plays]
- [sighs]
- [harrison wails]
- astor.
- mom!
- turn that down.
- we wouldn't have this problem
if you would just get me--
- this is not how you go about
getting an ipod.
Now, since you
woke your brother up,
You can walk him
around the living room
Until he falls asleep.
- but he never sleeps.
- think about that next time.
- there we go.
- you'd like an ipod,
wouldn't you, little harrison?
- [exhales]
Why not just end the terror
and give her an ipod?
- mm.
No, it's a power play.
She's trying to manipulate us
to get what she wants.
That's not how it works
in this family.
- oh, right.
of course.
- cody.
No more marco polo
in the mornings.
- but it's important.
- so is being ready
for school.
- when i grow up,
i want to be just like you.
Do what i want when i want.
- you and me both.
And i want to be
just like you.
[growls]
Marco.
- polo!
- great time last night,
huh, angel?
What?
You could've totally fucked
that stripper.
[elevator dings]
- get to work, gentlemen.
- what got into her?
[upbeat latin music]
? ?
- what is this?
extreme home makeover:
forensics edition?
- the first pass through,
i found some blood
That didn't belong
to the victim.
- possible dna from the killer?
- don't think so.
the sample was pretty degraded.
- then what's the source?
- not sure. yet.
- coming from you,
why does that not surprise me?
- you know
he's my brother, right?
- found something.
mr. morgan.
- hmm?
- it's blood.
Pool pattern,
not incidental spatter
From the recent murder.
This is something else
entirely.
- where's it from?
- bathtub.
- so you're taking an already
extremely difficult case
And polluting it with your,
what, theories?
- i didn't put the blood there.
- and according to you,
neither did our killer.
- joey,
why don't we step outside,
Let the geeks
get their geek on?
Look,
i gotta be somewhere,
So see if you can
hold things down around here
Without going all asshole
on my brother, okay?
- blood tells.
blood always tells.
- dexter.
How's my favorite
blood spatter analyst?
- uh, great.
How's my favorite
serial killer hunter?
Uh, you just missed deb.
- actually, i'm here
to see you.
- oh.
- database has a girl
killed here recently.
Severed femoral artery?
- pretty brutal.
- crime scene
telling you anything?
- not much.
- killer was careful, right?
Immaculate.
- very.
- well, you're in the middle
of something here.
I, uh, i don't want
to interrupt.
Mind if i drop by the station
later?
- sure, not a problem.
- good seeing you again,
dexter.
- shit.
[doorbell rings]
- hello, detective.
Won't you come in?
- i'm here to talk
about harry morgan.
I'm his daughter, debra.
Debra morgan.
- [exhales]
Handsome harry morgan.
how is he?
- he died a while back.
- life does tend to suck.
- did you and my father have...
A good relationship?
- well...
Your father
was a driven man.
He saw something he wanted,
nothing got in his way.
- you're talking about women?
- women.
bad guys.
Anything.
Anyone.
Harry always said
the only word
That wasn't in his vocabulary
was "no."
- did you say no to him?
- dear.
I said yes.
All the time.
Shit, hundreds of times.
Only problem was...
- only problem was what?
- i was saying yes to a question
he never asked.
- so you didn't have an affair
with my father?
- i don't know who
you're looking for, honey,
But it ain't me.
- shut down for decades.
way out of town.
I'm liking this.
Broken-down boxer,
broken-down arena.
A fitting place
for a punk
Like benny gomez
to go down for the count.
- where you been?
- [exhales]
Looking for misery.
- no upside to that.
- so i'm fucking learning.
- that's all we got
on the groom.
Plug was pulled
4:45 this morning.
It's all yours.
- [exhales]
A man's life and death,
reduced to a few...
What do you call 'em?
- bytes.
- a few bytes.
Just like that.
- this economy.
Last thing our city needs
is dead tourists.
- hey, welcome to miami.
Have a nice day.
- is that our tourist,
sergeant?
- it is, lieutenant.
- okay.
The mayor's already given me
an aneurysm over this one,
So make it a quick solve.
- okay.
- so whatever happened
between you
And that barbara gianna
from vice?
- we broke up.
Wanted different things.
- office romances.
Doomed before
they fucking start.
You mind if i ask her out?
- knock yourself out.
- the perfect husband would've
gotten rid of his old apartment.
But i kill people.
Not exactly
the perfect husband.
Someone new is moving in.
Be nice.
The land that time
and florida electric forgot.
Look at this place.
All the cheering,
all the triumph,
All the blood.
All for sport.
Until tonight.
[music and chatter inside bar]
Keep at it, benny,
and you'll be feeling no pain.
Better that way.
[snoring]
- tell me you got a reason
for sleeping alone in your car
Outside a bar
other than you're drunk.
- i'm tired.
- license and registration,
please.
- sorry about this, officer.
This is not
what it looks like.
- you're with homicide?
- yes, sir.
- then you ought
to know better.
Get out of the car,
please.
You know your abcs?
- of course i do.
- give me 'em backwards.
- uh...z, y, x, w...
V, u, t, s, r, q,
P, o,
L, m, k--
- clearly you're not drunk.
Yet.
- [sighs]
[engine revs up]
- damn it, benny.
I can't go
chasing after you
With a cop up my ass.
- you got more important places
to be, mr. morgan.
- [sighs]
Tell me about it.
- hey.
I thought
you were working late.
- so did i.
- mm.
Baby's down.
You know what that means?
- mm. sleep.
- sex.
- oh.
- and i'm not talking
the rushed, frantic,
The-kids-are-asleep sex.
But slow, hot, steamy,
naughty sex.
- look, if you're too tired...
- [moans]
Dexter, ever since the move
and the baby,
We've had, like,
zero time together.
- yeah.
- i mean, aren't you
as horny as i am?
- 'course i am.
- all right.
well, just close your eyes.
- maybe i can squeeze in
a power nap.
- okay, open.
- or not.
- i was saving these
for when we finally got
Some real time alone.
And...
And tonight's the night.
Mm.
[giggles]
- oh. ha ha...
- [giggles]
- [harrison cries]
- oh...
- mm.
- it's all right.
i'll go.
You've already done so much.
- [crying]
- oh, who's a good boy?
- yeah, who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy?
Yeah.
[whispering]
want to know a secret?
Daddy kills people.
Well, bad people.
Not really anybody else
i can tell about that,
You know?
Daddy's not going anywhere,
buddy.
I've already lost
my innocence.
I'm not going
to sacrifice yours too.
Triple red-eye, please.
- that's your third one
today, bro.
You don't cut back,
And you're tempting
the heart gods.
- least of my worries.
Bro.
- brought you a copy
of my article.
Figured you're a dumb cop
and don't read the paper.
- give me some credit.
i never miss the obituaries.
Front page.
nice.
- i do what i can.
My editor okayed a follow-up.
You got anything for me?
- i would if i could,
but i got nothing.
- hmm.
- besides, off the record?
We, uh,
got bigger fish to fry.
- what kind of fish?
Off the record.
- you know those pricks
Who've been
shaking down tourists?
- the vacation robbers?
- no, the vacation murderers.
They shot some poor newlywed.
didn't make it.
So...we're more than
a little distracted.
- you want
another distraction,
I'd love to take you out
for a drink.
You know, to thank you
for your help...
With the bathtub story.
- uh-huh.
- uh-uh.
i am so not hitting on you.
- yeah, me neither.
let's make it dinner.
- i got the blood work back
from our bathroom do-over.
- did you run it through
the database?
- no point.
The blood you swabbed
showed shit-all
On the dna front.
Our chances of finding out
who it belongs to
Are about, oh,
one in six fucking billion.
- what was lisa bell's address?
- 1578 glencoe.
why?
- well...
If the dna won't tell us
who it belonged to,
Maybe the address will.
- 1578 glencoe.
April 11, 1979.
homicide.
1979?
- vicky noonan, 22.
Found in the bathtub.
- bled out.
Incision to her thigh.
What are the chances of that?
- what are the chances of what?
- special agent lundy.
- vincent masuka,
if memory serves.
- that's right.
L.f.i. on the b.h.b.
- heh.
- you're working a case, right?
Feds need us to--
- mind if i speak with dexter?
- uh...i'll go, uh,
to records
And get the write-up
on noonan.
Just doing my job.
- he's right, you know.
- about?
- why i'm in miami.
It is a case.
- yeah, i figured.
But why do you need me?
You have the full resources
of the fbi.
- not anymore.
I'm retired.
- oh.
Their loss.
- yeah, well.
I fish. travel.
And, uh...
Now i have the time
to track down
The one twisted
son of a bitch who got away.
- so who is
the twisted son of a bitch?
- i call him
the trinity killer.
Kills in threes.
Been doing it all over
the country for years.
Problem is,
i can't prove he exists.
Law enforcement
doesn't talk to each other.
So no one at the fbi
is even on board.
Just me.
I've been looking for a break.
Then this happens.
- lisa bell.
- her murder profile
fits the previous victims.
Trinity's in miami, dexter.
Starting his cycle
all over again.
- no...no...
No...
- how far back
do your cases go?
- about 15 years.
- the house and room
where lisa bell was murdered
Was the site
of a very similar homicide
30 years ago.
Take a look.
- [sobbing]
No...no...
- we've come full circle.
He's back
where his killing began.
30 years.
You know what this means?
- trinity's the most
successful serial killer
To ever...
Get away with it.
- [moaning]
- what? i'm fine.
i can't wait to see you.
Anton, i have to go.
i have a meeting.
- hello, debra.
- motherfucking fuck.
- [chuckles]
Nice to see you too.
- what are...
What--
what are you doing here?
Are you here on a case?
- actually, i'm retired now.
- yet you're here.
- life has a natural
forward momentum.
Certain things are inevitable.
Like you.
Making detective.
Congratulations.
- thanks.
- i never had any doubt.
- [small laugh]
So how long
will your forward momentum
Keep you in miami?
- not sure exactly.
Be seeing you.
- yeah.
I guess. maybe.
I mean, i don't--
i don't know.
- big plans this evening,
sergeant?
- the usual, lieutenant.
[elevator dings]
- oh.
Hey, guys.
Drinks?
- i had benny gomez on the ropes
and let him slip away.
No way i can go
to that bar again.
Officer alphabet
made sure of that.
Which means i grab benny
where he lives.
A higher degree of difficulty,
but i don't have a choice.
If i want to be around
for my son,
I have to do this right.
I'm...killing for two now.
[man speaking spanish on tv]
- the fuck you want?
- you.
- look at him.
fast asleep.
Lucky guy.
- i know you.
[muffled]
- i'm the blood guy.
You've made a lot of people
very miserable.
Me included.
[exhales]
Till now.
Oh...
Because now i get to answer
life's big question.
My life, anyway.
Can i do it?
can i have it all?
[cell phone rings]
- oh, shit.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
- dexter, i need you to go to an
all-night pharmacy right away.
- i'm kind of
in the middle of something.
- well, harrison has
an ear infection.
He's in a lot of pain,
dexter.
Whatever you're doing can wait.
- uh, right. my mistake.
i wasn't thinking.
I'm on my way.
Kids.
Gotta go.
Clock's ticking.
But it's all about sacrifice.
- [muffled scream]
- for the good of the family.
- maybe tonight wasn't perfect.
Maybe i need to reboot
the way i do things.
But at least
i'm on the right road.
I'm on my way
to taking care of my family,
Raising my son.
And all the while
doing what i have to do
To satisfy a calling
that i can't ignore...
Or deny.
I can do this.
- dexter!
You don't need to sleep!
You need to wake up!
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org